

Elankumaran SivaSubramaniam

BSc (Hons) in Software Engineering

🔀 siva98kumarane@gmail.com 🤰 0763762180

Annavasa" Kaithady West Kaithady, 40000 Jaffna

Education

B.Sc (Hons) in Software Engineering

02/2019 - 06/2023

University Of Kelaniya, Kelaniya

GPA: 2.82

G.C.E Advance Level (Physical Science)

01/2009 - 08/2017

J/Chavakachcheri Hindu College, Chavakachcheri

Combine Mathematics: - A

Chemistry:- B Physics: - B

Employment

Web Developer Freelancer

09/2023 - Present

Hotflix

Admin Dashboard creation for web

• Developed a versatile and user-friendly admin dashboard with data visualization features.

IMDB Data Fetching using Id

• Created a tool to efficiently fetch IMDb IDs, improving content retrieval for movie-related projects.

Associate Software Engineer

04/2023 - 09/2023

Techscrolll, Colombo

- User Interface Development For Tuber-3
- Implemented Redux for state management in that project.
- API Integration for map features

Software Engineer Intern

09/2021 - 02/2022

Gypzeez, Colombo

- Developed and maintained React-based application(Shopping App), ensuring a high level of functionality and performance.
- Developed and implemented new features using React hooks.
- Learn about Full Stack Web Development

Courses

Alison Frontend Development

04/2021

Alison Operation Systems Courses

02/2021

Personal details

LinkedIn

linkedin.

com/in/elankumaransivasubramaniam

About

A highly skilled and motivated MERN Stack developer with Internship and working experience in developing user-friendly and efficient web applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express js MongoDB and Redux. Strong understanding of React lifecycle methods and hooks.

Github

github.com/Elankumaran98

| Skills | S | ki | | S |
|--------|---|----|--|---|
|--------|---|----|--|---|

React Js

Node Js

MongoDB

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Git

Web Development

Projects

Projects

- Country Based Name Predictor
- :- React Application Using Predict Name country based.
 - ProHub (Project management application)
- :-Developed reusable UI components to reduce development time (React).
- :-Used Agile methodology for software development and worked in a fast-paced environment.

| Express Js | |
|------------|---|
| Bootstrap | _ |
| Figma | |
| | |
| Languages | |
| Tamil | |
| English | |
| Sinhala | |
| | |
| | |

Hobbies

- Playing Cricket
- Reading Books
- Playing Mobile Games